Wade Brown: Hey, Gary.
UNKNOWN: Hi.
David Mendenhall: Hey, can you put your characters on Initiative Tracker 3.0?
Gary Young [?]: 3.0.
Gary Young: Okay, I want.
Gary Young: How are you doing?
David Mendenhall: Good.
David Mendenhall: How are you?
Gary Young: Atlanta is going okay.
David Mendenhall: Good.
David Mendenhall: You're going to be there for two weeks?
Gary Young: I'm in Atlanta for one week and then Bangalore for two weeks.
David Mendenhall: Bangalore for two weeks.
David Mendenhall: Oh, okay.
Gary Young: So, unfortunately, I did not write a backstory yet.
David Mendenhall: But do you know the backstory?
David Mendenhall: I was just going to tell everybody what it was.
Gary Young: Maybe partially.
David Mendenhall: Enough.
David Mendenhall: You can be mysterious.
David Mendenhall: You can be all shadowhardy.
Gary Young: Yeah, not shadowhardy.
Gary Young: No.
David Mendenhall: You don't have to tell us all your full backstory.
David Mendenhall: Brewbarry.
David Mendenhall: Good name.
David Mendenhall: I like that one.
Gary Young: We're going to do the consistent plus twos here on initiative.
David Mendenhall: That's funny.
David Mendenhall: I'll take the alert feet when I can.
Kostadis Roussos: Hello, hello.
Kostadis Roussos: I need icons.
David Mendenhall: I think we put them in the chat for you.
Kostadis Roussos: You did?
David Mendenhall: I did.
David Mendenhall: I did mine last week.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, well, you're better than me.
David Mendenhall: Yep, I am.
Kostadis Roussos: You're like always better than me.
Kostadis Roussos: You are always the best.
David Mendenhall: Oh, my gosh.
David Mendenhall: This guy.
David Mendenhall: I need Wade.
David Mendenhall[?]: All right.
David Mendenhall: There's Wade.
David Mendenhall: Hey, Wade, can you put your character in Initiative Tracker 3.0?
Wade Brown: I believe I can.
Wade Brown: Hold on.
Wade Brown: Let me get everything else set up here.
Wade Brown: Sorry, I'm late.
UNKNOWN: You're right on time.
Kostadis Roussos: You're not late because Kostadis didn't do his job.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: You had a job?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: I had to get the tokens ready.
David Mendenhall: You're making the tokens from our from the image we posted to the chat.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: For future reference, you too can make these with token marker.
David Mendenhall: Token maker?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, token maker.
David Mendenhall: Token maker.
Gary Young: In fact, if you want, it's easier to just make you do it, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
David Mendenhall: Exactly.
Kostadis Roussos: Plus, it deprives me of an opportunity to futz with your tokens in a way that I find satisfying.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
David Mendenhall: Let me tell everybody my backstory.
David Mendenhall: So Vukradin is a.
Kostadis Roussos: Are you going to write it down so I have it written down?
Wade Brown [?]: Or do you want us to write them down?
David Mendenhall: That's why we have this recorded.
David Mendenhall: And have you turned on the AI companion?
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Oh, wait.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Hold on.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Let me turn it on.
David Mendenhall: Turn on the AI companion and then it will write it for you.
Kostadis Roussos: I think I have it by default turned on.
David Mendenhall: I don't see the little icon.
David Mendenhall[?]: Right.
David Mendenhall: Here, ask host.
David Mendenhall: There we go.
David Mendenhall: Now it's on.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
David Mendenhall: Vukradin is a serious musician from what are we doing?
Kostadis Roussos [?]: None of that silly music.
UNKNOWN: Neverwinter, Neverwinter.
David Mendenhall: Neverwinter from Neverwinter.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Yes.
David Mendenhall: And he plays in a piano bar seven days a week and somehow never manages to make any money.
David Mendenhall: The patrons don't seem to care very much for the music he plays, but he works very hard.
David Mendenhall: And he's broke because he's not making any money from his piano bar despite working very hard.
David Mendenhall: So he's going to try adventuring because he's heard that there's a lot of money in it.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
David Mendenhall: And he's broke.
David Mendenhall: He's done.
David Mendenhall: He's very desperate.
Kostadis Roussos: He's desperate.
Kostadis Roussos: But does he want to be an adventurer?
Kostadis Roussos: This is kind of one of those things he's doing.
David Mendenhall: No, no, he wants to be a musician.
David Mendenhall: He wants to open like, you know, a music studio and play his serious music with other people who are serious with him and not just piano bar patrons.
David Mendenhall: But sometimes you got to do the things you have to do.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Sometimes.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So, Gary, this is your drow character.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Wade, do you have a turtle?
Wade Brown: I have a turtle.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I saw the very silly turtle image.
Kostadis Roussos: Is that the one you want me to use, or do you want me to use something more efficient?
Wade Brown [?]: Fine.
Wade Brown: No, no.
Wade Brown: I played around a bit.
Kostadis Roussos: No, I don't care.
Kostadis Roussos: It's like, you know, there's a rule of DD that no matter how stupid you make your character, in the end, he always turns serious.
Wade Brown: No, let me let me.
Wade Brown [?]: No, I'm lucky never turned serious.
Wade Brown [?]: Yeah, he did.
David Mendenhall: Unlucky became like a caricature.
Wade Brown [?]: Yeah.
Wade Brown: Sorry.
David Mendenhall[?]: I'm having things to do.
Wade Brown: I just got to export this.
Wade Brown: Where the heck is PNG?
Kostadis Roussos: I think that's the right moment.
Wade Brown: There it is.
Wade Brown: All right.
Wade Brown: Yes.
Wade Brown: Come on.
Wade Brown: I'm sorry.
Wade Brown: I'm not.
Wade Brown: I'm not ready.
Wade Brown: Go on.
Wade Brown: Go on without me for a moment.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So keep telling us about your backstory, man.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Who me or David?
Kostadis Roussos: David, David.
David Mendenhall: Oh, no, I'm done.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Gary, what's your backstory?
David Mendenhall: Very simple.
David Mendenhall: More will be revealed in time.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I figured.
Kostadis Roussos: Gary, your backstory?
David Mendenhall: I think we lost, Gary.
Kostadis Roussos: Gary.
David Mendenhall: What the hell?
David Mendenhall: Upside down, cat.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Why is this misbehaving?
Wade Brown [?]: Because it hates you.
Wade Brown: I know.
Wade Brown: I'm just.
Wade Brown: There you go.
Wade Brown: Did that work?
Wade Brown: What the heck is going on here?
David Mendenhall[?]: Are you trying to?
Wade Brown: Oh, I have to hit enter.
Wade Brown: I don't know.
Wade Brown: It just looked like it was posting it and then didn't and then stopped.
David Mendenhall: Or right arrow.
David Mendenhall: Right arrow sometimes works.
Wade Brown: Yeah, it's all right.
Wade Brown: I'm getting there.
Wade Brown [?]: Okay.
Wade Brown: Did we lose Gary?
David Mendenhall: Temporarily.
David Mendenhall: Oh, wow.
David Mendenhall: That's a very, that's a very serious image.
David Mendenhall: Wow.
David Mendenhall: He looks.
Wade Brown [?]: Oh, I love it.
David Mendenhall: Quite peaceful.
Wade Brown [?]: Quite peaceful.
Wade Brown: Yes.
Wade Brown: It's a she.
Wade Brown: It's a lady turtle.
Wade Brown [?]: Oh, I didn't realize that.
UNKNOWN: Very peaceful.
Kostadis Roussos: Are you playing a she?
Kostadis Roussos: Is that what I'm supposed to infer?
Wade Brown: Yes.
Wade Brown: Okay.
Wade Brown: Is that going to be a problem?
David Mendenhall[?]: No, no, no, no.
David Mendenhall[?]: No, no.
David Mendenhall: Gary has played women several times.
Kostadis Roussos: In fact, one time he played two women at the same time.
Kostadis Roussos: It was very awkward.
Kostadis Roussos: One was a cleric and one was a paladin, and they kept possessing each other's bodies.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Okay, that's a little bizarre.
David Mendenhall: Oh, yeah.
David Mendenhall: I do faintly remember that.
Wade Brown: What is this like your name?
David Mendenhall: Did you have to like roll to see who was successful or something?
Wade Brown [?]: Yes.
David Mendenhall[?]: Periodically.
Wade Brown: Oh, we had a split personality.
Wade Brown: That must have been fun to deal with.
David Mendenhall: Right.
David Mendenhall: It was a split personality.
David Mendenhall[?]: Yeah.
Wade Brown [?]: It was awesome.
David Mendenhall: An interesting character idea.
Kostadis Roussos: It definitely was the most interesting one.
Kostadis Roussos: It was one of the more interesting ones.
Kostadis Roussos: It didn't quite reach level or Orsik level of excitement, but you know.
Wade Brown: Can I find me?
David Mendenhall[?]: Yeah.
David Mendenhall[?]: This is the right.
David Mendenhall[?]: We want something bright for her.
Wade Brown: I don't remember where to find Spell DC to fill that in.
David Mendenhall: So to spells.
Wade Brown [?]: Yeah.
Wade Brown: There's the modifier, the spell attack, and the save DC.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, that's it.
David Mendenhall[?]: It's right up there.
Wade Brown [?]: That's it to sell save DC.
David Mendenhall[?]: Oh, it's a save DC.
UNKNOWN: Okay.
David Mendenhall: Save DC.
Wade Brown: I was looking right at it.
Wade Brown: I was like, I'm not sure which one to put in.
Wade Brown: Let's see.
Wade Brown: Passive perception.
Wade Brown: Passive investigation.
Wade Brown: I'm kind of blind.
Wade Brown: Passive insight.
David Mendenhall: Well, Valphine has 1515.
David Mendenhall: Wow.
David Mendenhall: Well, we don't have anybody with like three hit points, so that's good.
Wade Brown: Unlucky did fine.
David Mendenhall: He somehow managed to make it to the end of the adventure.
Wade Brown: Well, he ended up getting like the stone of soak 100 HP damage or something.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Yeah.
UNKNOWN: I mean, I think he got that pretty low by the end.
Kostadis Roussos: And plus, he had the most amazing resource ever.
Wade Brown: A cleric?
Wade Brown [?]: Pocket cleric?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, he had a walking band-aid.
Kostadis Roussos: So he didn't actually have 50 hit points.
Kostadis Roussos: He had 50 hit points plus whatever the healing maximum of the cleric was.
Kostadis Roussos: Right?
Kostadis Roussos: That's how it works, right?
Kostadis Roussos [?]: That's how it works.
David Mendenhall: So we've got a druid, a bard, a barbarian, and a cleric.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Now I have to get your.
Kostadis Roussos: I got the tokens.
Kostadis Roussos: I need to go do one more thing.
Kostadis Roussos: Get your names.
Kostadis Roussos: Hey, can you claim your character?
Kostadis Roussos: And it's like, I know it doesn't actually matter, but it's kind of one of those.
Wade Brown: You're such a white.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: No, I'll do it.
David Mendenhall: I did that, right?
David Mendenhall[?]: I didn't.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: I definitely did not.
Kostadis Roussos: It like, I know it doesn't matter, and I know it's not important, but it really is important to me.
David Mendenhall: It helps you because you have so many campaigns.
Wade Brown: It's fine.
Wade Brown: I've done.
Wade Brown: I've clicked the camp, whatever.
Wade Brown: I'm going to unassign Vardis.
Wade Brown: Oh, I can't.
David Mendenhall[?]: He's deactivated.
UNKNOWN: All right.
UNKNOWN: Well, never mind then.
Wade Brown: Rest in peace, Vardis.
David Mendenhall: Neverwinter, huh?
David Mendenhall: At some point, I'd like to go to the piano bar and Neverwinter.
Kostadis Roussos: We could do that.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Of course, we could do that.
David Mendenhall: That's a ways away, though.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, create a character.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: What's the name of this character?
Kostadis Roussos: Valphine Sotorra.
Kostadis Roussos: Hey, we haven't still gotten Gary's version of the story.
David Mendenhall: He's going to join in a moment.
Kostadis Roussos: By the way, did you like your background?
David Mendenhall[?]: Huh?
David Mendenhall[?]: I gave you a- Oh, I thought that was that AI-generated, Kostadis?
Wade Brown [?]: No, I actually created it by myself.
David Mendenhall: Wow.
Wade Brown: Oh, now I feel bad that I was thinking it was just as an example.
David Mendenhall: I just assumed it was AI-generated.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no.
Wade Brown: No, I mean, I thought it was fun.
UNKNOWN: I just don't want to be attached to nobility or anything.
Wade Brown: I figured you're not attached to nobility.
Wade Brown: She's born, you know, lived out of the house.
Kostadis Roussos: She's not attached to no noble.
Wade Brown: No, she's familiar with the noble lifestyle while not being in it.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I figured that was the kind of resentment you would like.
Wade Brown: Jeez.
Wade Brown: No, I mean, it's fine.
Kostadis Roussos: I just wasn't do whatever you want.
Kostadis Roussos: I gave you some input.
Kostadis Roussos: Like, give us a background.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Yeah.
David Mendenhall: Gary.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Hi.
Gary Young [?]: Sorry.
Kostadis Roussos: I have to do two more.
David Mendenhall: Gary, do you have any backstory to share?
Gary Young [?]: Not really.
Gary Young [?]: I'm so disappointed.
Gary Young [?]: I know.
Kostadis Roussos: You should be disappointed.
Kostadis Roussos: And this is very unfortunate.
Kostadis Roussos: We will have to resort to background by screenwriters over time.
David Mendenhall: Or roll.
David Mendenhall: Roll for background.
Wade Brown: It's a pleasure to meet you.
David Mendenhall: Exactly.
David Mendenhall: Plus one mace.
Wade Brown [?]: Yeah.
Gary Young: So, you know, we have a Drow, a drow cleric of, I think I said Lathander, didn't I?
David Mendenhall[?]: Yes.
David Mendenhall: Very good drone cleric.
Kostadis Roussos: No, she's embracing.
Kostadis Roussos: She's embracing herself.
David Mendenhall: She's embracing the light.
Gary Young: She's masochistic.
Gary Young: She likes pain.
Gary Young: And so, okay.
David Mendenhall: Has she developed a tolerance to the light?
Kostadis Roussos [?]: No, no, she likes it.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Wow.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: If only she had a shell she could retreat into.
David Mendenhall: Like a permanent disadvantage, huh?
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, they don't have disadvantage anymore in fifth edition.
Kostadis Roussos: They don't, do they?
Kostadis Roussos: I don't think so.
Kostadis Roussos: No, they don't.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, they don't.
Gary Young: Yeah.
Gary Young: So that's at least Valphine right now.
Gary Young: And then Brewbarry, I don't know that I have a background for him either, but he's, you know, like the Goliath Uthgardt barbarian.
Gary Young: And I don't know that I fully figured out like how he's there with the Uthgardt.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, it's close by, physically.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah. He could, I mean, depending on where he, I mean, so the real question is, did how did Valphine and the Barbarian meet?
Gary Young: Oh, should are we assuming that they met first?
Gary Young [?]: How did you all beat?
Gary Young [?]: Or you all show up in Phandalin, you know, traveling.
David Mendenhall: I'm following this like get rich quick flyer that was posted in Neverwinter.
Wade Brown: Oh, see, my plan for backstory was to have her running as a guide.
Wade Brown: She could be leading people back into town or whatever, at least to get her at the party.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: That seems like a perfect setup for the musician and the turtle.
Wade Brown: Yes.
Wade Brown: In her sunset year, she's just leading tours around the forest, guiding adventurers to other places.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: You know, you don't know where you don't adventure, right?
Kostadis Roussos: You're a bard.
Kostadis Roussos: You're a musician.
Kostadis Roussos: You're too good for this life.
David Mendenhall[?]: Yeah.
David Mendenhall: I'm slumming it.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: And when she offers to give you a tour, you say yes.
Kostadis Roussos: And when she asks to be paid, you say there's this thing called adventuring.
Wade Brown: I'll pay you in a song.
Wade Brown: Oh, great.
David Mendenhall: Wait, I have to pay her?
David Mendenhall: I thought I got paid.
David Mendenhall: The flyer said I would be paid.
Gary Young: I think Brewbarry.
David Mendenhall: I don't have any money.
Gary Young [?]: Oh, dear.
Gary Young [?]: You'll have to work it off.
Gary Young: I think Brewbarry, when he was, let's go with kicked out of the Uthgardt Barbarian.
David Mendenhall: He's kicked out.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
Gary Young: I think for being a drunk, I think we might go with that.
David Mendenhall[?]: Hey, it's Uncle June.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, Uncle June.
Gary Young: Maybe not that bad.
Gary Young: A little bit of a let's go with a dopey giant sort of character.
David Mendenhall[?]: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: Does the Aasimar have a light night vision?
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Drow?
UNKNOWN: No, no, I'm talking about the Aasimar.
David Mendenhall[?]: Vukradin.
David Mendenhall: Aasimar has, yeah, it has dark vision, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: What's the range of it?
Gary Young: We want to put this on the tracker.
Gary Young [?]: No, no, I need it for putting it in.
David Mendenhall: 60 feet.
David Mendenhall: All right.
David Mendenhall[?]: Okay.
Gary Young [?]: All right.
Gary Young [?]: Okay, keep going.
Gary Young: And then so he got kicked out of the Uthgardt for being too much of a drunk.
Gary Young: And then, you know, like as he stumbled into town, he just wanted some friends.
Gary Young: And then the flyer offered, you know, like someone to hang out with.
Gary Young: So with that as a motivation.
David Mendenhall: Casual.
David Mendenhall: Sure, let's go around the forest together.
David Mendenhall: That'll be fun.
Gary Young: It was lonely.
Gary Young: I needed someone to hang out with.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
David Mendenhall: I can play you a song.
David Mendenhall: Do you like songs?
Kostadis Roussos: I do.
David Mendenhall: Oh, perfect.
Kostadis Roussos: Hey, does I don't think turtles have night vision, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Wade, do turtles have night vision?
Wade Brown: I'm muted.
Wade Brown: I'm saying I don't believe they do.
David Mendenhall: So go to features and traits.
Wade Brown: I don't see it anywhere in the usual.
UNKNOWN: Yeah, no, it's fine.
David Mendenhall[?]: She doesn't need it.
Wade Brown [?]: Excellent.
UNKNOWN: I have a light spell, so we can just cast light.
UNKNOWN: Light Cantrip.
Wade Brown [?]: We can just cast light whenever we need it.
Wade Brown: We can just roll in a shell and tumble down the hill like a boulder.
Gary Young: My drow cleric would love to cast light spells for me.
Wade Brown [?]: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: It hurts myself.
Kostadis Roussos: I just want to say that your cleric is very conflicted about her role in life.
Gary Young: I think she's not conflicted at all.
Gary Young: But how she got here and how she found this particular path that is something that will need some thought.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, but does she know the barbarian?
Kostadis Roussos: Does she meet the barbarian, or is the barbarian picked up from Neverwinter from a bar, the same piano bar that David Mendenhallwas that Vukradin?
Kostadis Roussos: Like, you know, the barbarian was a drunk in the bar.
Kostadis Roussos: He was being kicked out because he didn't pay his bills.
Kostadis Roussos: Vukradin made a claim that, you know, I know where we can make money.
UNKNOWN: I've got his paper.
Gary Young: I think he probably showed up at the bar lonely and then looking for someone to drink with.
Gary Young [?]: All right.
Gary Young [?]: Okay.
David Mendenhall: I drink at the bar.
David Mendenhall: I play piano.
Gary Young: Oh.
Gary Young: I drink tea.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
David Mendenhall: Follow tales only.
Kostadis Roussos: Like maybe.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, wait.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me give you another.
Kostadis Roussos: The barbarian actually finds the music that Vukradin to be amazing.
David Mendenhall: It is amazing.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no.
Kostadis Roussos: Like, like, he, it's like, for him, this is like the music of the ages.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Let's say he grew up with Uthgardt music, which is just drums.
Gary Young: And like, all these pitches and tones are like amazing.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, it's like he's just, you know, so like he's like your biggest fan.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: There we go.
Kostadis Roussos: That's not just your biggest fan, but he also gets really offended when other people don't share in the enthusiastic appraisal of your music.
David Mendenhall: Me too.
David Mendenhall[?]: Yeah, I'm just, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, let's go with that.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: That's good.
David Mendenhall: Well, that's nice of you guys.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: I just want to make sure we're all okay with that.
Kostadis Roussos: No issues.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: David?
David Mendenhall: Sure.
David Mendenhall[?]: Did that work?
Kostadis Roussos: What?
David Mendenhall: Make that work?
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, he doesn't have to always like it.
Kostadis Roussos: He could at some point decide that, you know, the music sucks.
David Mendenhall: Well, I don't have a piano with me.
David Mendenhall: So I'm going to have to fall back to like flute and clarinet in camp.
Wade Brown [?]: That's fine. All right. Teach me the drums. I'm not a percussionist. Maybe the barbarian can help you with that. No. Percussion is really boring.
Wade Brown: It makes the song.
Gary Young: And too much of that.
Gary Young: And it makes my head pound after drinking.
Wade Brown: The drinking is what makes your head pound.
Gary Young [?]: Okay.
Gary Young [?]: The total perfect.
UNKNOWN: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: I think it's a look.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Download.
Kostadis Roussos: Okie dokie.
Kostadis Roussos: And then all right.
Kostadis Roussos: So it.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Next thing I need to do is I need to invite you to this adventure.
David Mendenhall: Yes.
David Mendenhall: I'm rolling.
David Mendenhall: You could delete some of these.
David Mendenhall: You could delete old and be one guys.
Kostadis Roussos: I don't delete them, but I can archive them.
Wade Brown: There's no sense in deleting anything with cloud storage.
Wade Brown: It's infinite.
Wade Brown [?]: Yes, exactly.
David Mendenhall: Amazing.
David Mendenhall: We've created an infinite storage.
David Mendenhall[?]: Somebody else is paying for it.
UNKNOWN: It's infinite to me.
Wade Brown: What are you up to, idiot?
Wade Brown: All right.
Wade Brown: Sorry.
Wade Brown: I don't put that in the middle.
David Mendenhall[?]: What do you cat doing?
David Mendenhall: We don't see very much.
Wade Brown: You won't see her in here, not with the dog around.
Wade Brown: They have lots of roll 20 link in the chat.
Wade Brown: Now I got to find which of these seven chats.
Wade Brown [?]: All right, there it is.
Wade Brown [?]: Google chat.
David Mendenhall[?]: Yeah.
Wade Brown: Icespire.
Wade Brown [?]: What?
Gary Young: I don't have to accept this invitation.
Kostadis Roussos: You just have to click on that link and do whatever it says.
Kostadis Roussos: I don't actually know what it says.
David Mendenhall: Why am I so much smaller than everybody else?
Kostadis Roussos: You're not smaller than everybody else.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: You are?
David Mendenhall[?]: No, he is.
David Mendenhall: I'm definitely smaller.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: He is definitely smaller.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, because I felt that if I didn't have your musical instrument, it would be somehow demeaning.
Kostadis Roussos: I could create a new image.
David Mendenhall: It's fine.
David Mendenhall: I can be small.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, I hate to say this, but visual.
David Mendenhall[?]: Let me just say back.
UNKNOWN: Visual arts was never your thing.
David Mendenhall: No.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: And so this was the best.
David Mendenhall: But I have a great appreciation for all the arts.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I thought.
David Mendenhall: It wasn't my thing.
David Mendenhall: This wasn't, you know, not something I was tanned to at.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Wade Brown: Why can't I get rid of this turn order thing?
Wade Brown [?]: What turn order thing?
Wade Brown: I don't know.
Wade Brown: That little turn order thing on roll 20.
David Mendenhall: Oh, yeah.
David Mendenhall: I hate that thing.
Wade Brown [?]: Oh, that's because I have to click on it.
David Mendenhall[?]: Oh, you have to delete it.
David Mendenhall[?]: Okay, I was wondering.
David Mendenhall: You can shrink it a little bit and then put it in the corner.
Wade Brown: I've never seen it before.
Wade Brown: Now, you know, it's all I see.
Wade Brown [?]: Oh, wow.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Wade Brown [?]: Launch game.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Gary, Wade, David, we have all joined.
David Mendenhall: Alrighty.
Kostadis Roussos: All righty.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Establishment calming down.
Gary Young: So do so.
Gary Young: So what does this flyer set again?
Gary Young: The flyers hang around.
David Mendenhall: It said, come to Phandalin.
Gary Young [?]: Phandalin?
David Mendenhall: Phandalin?
David Mendenhall: Is that where we are?
Gary Young [?]: Phandalin.
Kostadis Roussos: Phandalin.
David Mendenhall: Phandalin.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: I don't know.
UNKNOWN: I just followed Brewbarry.
David Mendenhall: It said, come here and easy money shall be yours.
Kostadis Roussos: What it said, what it said was: with the end of the War of the Giants and the War of the Dragons, the hinterland of Neverwinter is in need of adventurers and heroes to bring peace and prosperity.
UNKNOWN: No, no, that's not right.
UNKNOWN: It definitely said something about money.
David Mendenhall: I mean, I'm all for peace and prosperity.
David Mendenhall: I totally believe in that.
David Mendenhall: But at this point, I'm having trouble buying food to eat.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, I'm sorry.
Kostadis Roussos: So it's like, are you adventures, heroes, people who want to make a change?
Kostadis Roussos: The kingdom, Neverwinter needs you.
David Mendenhall: Phandalin.
Kostadis Roussos: No, Phandalin.
David Mendenhall[?]: Neverwinter needs you.
Kostadis Roussos: Phandalin happens to be an ally as part of the hinterland of Neverwinter.
Kostadis Roussos: And Lord Neverember wants you to go help him secure the territories.
David Mendenhall: Was he literally named Lord Neverember?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, Neverember.
Kostadis Roussos: I did not come up with a eunuch.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
David Mendenhall: And a Gygax special Neverember?
Kostadis Roussos: Dude, I did not come up with it.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Wow.
David Mendenhall[?]: No, it was not invented by Gygax.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Sounds like we needed a new mayor.
David Mendenhall: We'll take care of that in a future adventure, yes.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Is Wallace still around?
David Mendenhall: We're going to need a better name for sure.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, Wallace is not only around, he's got kids now.
David Mendenhall: That's right.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Don't we all?
UNKNOWN: Orsik's hanging out with him, taking care of the kids.
Gary Young [?]: Yeah, it's, you know, yeah.
Gary Young: I'm having a little trouble hooking Valphine here.
Gary Young: So I don't think she sees herself as a hero.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Gary Young: The lure of like maybe learning the hardships of traveling on the road, like that, that might be something.
Gary Young [?]: She's not the hero type, right?
Gary Young: Why is this going to be a bad experience for her?
Gary Young: Like, that's what she needs to know.
Kostadis Roussos: It doesn't have to be a bad experience.
Kostadis Roussos: There's nothing about this that says it has to be bad.
Gary Young: Well, I mean, this is her motivation is like inflicting pain on herself.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, on that's going to be a weird one for my girl.
David Mendenhall: That's going to be a weird one.
David Mendenhall: Did not see that.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: She's not going to want to see your girl suffer.
Kostadis Roussos: But is it suffering if it's something you want to happen to yourself?
Wade Brown: If you want it, then it's not suffering.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, then you and her can have a wonderfully long and complex conversation.
Gary Young [?]: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: But, you know, like that's part of the Lathander and Drow combo. There we go. Okay. So let's see. Okay. All righty. Okay. So hold on. Let me just do one more thing. That should not be here. There we go. All right. So.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: So, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: So what the.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me do as I say.
Kostadis Roussos: So.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: There's just one more thing I need to do, which is open 12.
Kostadis Roussos: This is the.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Can you guys see your player token?
Wade Brown: I can see a box of four player tokens.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, great.
Kostadis Roussos: So that is my new convention for.
Kostadis Roussos: I don't know whether I did it with my last campaign.
Wade Brown: You didn't do it with us last time.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Just do us as individuals.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so I discovered this.
Kostadis Roussos: This is a much easier way of having all four of you on the map.
Wade Brown [?]: All right.
Wade Brown: I mean, you could just say like party and have like a little party balloon or something.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, but this is prettier.
Wade Brown: It is.
Wade Brown: I can see that I'm in the bottom right as I belong.
David Mendenhall: What's the symbolism of the bottom right?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, you got me worried there, man.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: So, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So just to remind you, so Neverwinter managed to survive the storm known as the War of the Dragons.
Kostadis Roussos: It managed to survive the storm known as the War of the Giants.
Kostadis Roussos: And now, after several managed to survive the barbarian hordes that made it.
David Mendenhall: Is that what's been going on?
David Mendenhall: For like the last five years, that's been happening?
David Mendenhall: I missed all of that.
Wade Brown [?]: Yes, yes.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: The land has been crying out.
UNKNOWN: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Neverwinter had, you know, Neverwinter was strategically placed sufficiently far away from the hordes of the Uthgardtian barbarians that after the War of the Giants ended, was able to avoid the worst of the tribal wars.
Gary Young: Yeah, the barbarians.
Gary Young: Yeah, that was.
Kostadis Roussos: But now, now, now, what is it?
Kostadis Roussos: Now, Neverwinter is all about growth, advancing, making things better.
Kostadis Roussos: And, you know, after having had some trouble to the north with its hinterland, it's proposing to re-establish trade and outposts to the south.
Kostadis Roussos: And one of those is Phandalin.
Kostadis Roussos: Phandalin has been having trouble.
Kostadis Roussos: And because Lord Neverember, well, there's limited budget, limited limited member, limited resources.
Kostadis Roussos: And, you know, he's come up with a brilliant scheme, hiring adventures.
Kostadis Roussos: For those of you in the management biz, he's going with contractors because they have fewer benefits.
Gary Young: That's our thing.
Kostadis Roussos: And as his convention, anybody who does a good turn for the kingdom can keep whatever the gold and treasure they want, etc.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, if you ever had enough money for taxes, that's what he meant.
David Mendenhall: Oh, no, it's tax-free income, is what you're telling me.
Wade Brown [?]: Yes, it's tax-free.
Wade Brown: Well, that's not typical for $10.99.
David Mendenhall: Okay, well.
Kostadis Roussos: So the paper.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so the paper is calling all adventurers to head south, to go clear the hinterland of monsters, enemies of Neverwinter, and re-establish civilization and the march of progress.
David Mendenhall: And after we clear a monster, then what do we do?
Wade Brown: Do you bring their scalps?
Wade Brown: Seems vile.
David Mendenhall: Do we take them to Lord Neverember?
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no.
Wade Brown: Like a cat delivering a dead mouse.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, so I'm going to assume that you're.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm going to assume that as you pick up this notice, a guard is standing next, a guard is standing next to you in Neverwinter and says, looks at you with this quirky expression and says, no, please, for the love of goodness, all that is good, do not bring anything to his lordship.
Kostadis Roussos: Why do you ask?
Kostadis Roussos: Are you asking about how you make the money?
David Mendenhall: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: He pauses and goes, well, I am, of course, an official city guard and get paid on a regular basis, have benefits.
David Mendenhall: So, like that.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm off.
Kostadis Roussos: That is not how adventures get paid.
Kostadis Roussos: You are an adventurer, or at least this is what we're looking to hire.
Kostadis Roussos: And the way they make money is by defeating the monsters and securing whatever trinkets and treasure they might have amongst their goods.
Wade Brown [?]: So we just loot them.
David Mendenhall: You just take the money from the monsters?
David Mendenhall: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: It's an excellent system.
Kostadis Roussos: We get what we want.
David Mendenhall: Where did the monsters get that money from?
Kostadis Roussos: I don't know.
Kostadis Roussos: And to be quite honest with you, Lord Neverember and the guard don't care.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, but I care.
Kostadis Roussos: You aren't going to be very wealthy in this adventuring business if you care too much about these details.
David Mendenhall: Well, now, I'm not super dumb.
David Mendenhall: I mean, I can imagine the monsters got the money from killing people.
David Mendenhall: Yes.
David Mendenhall: And so, rightfully, that money belongs to their heirs.
David Mendenhall[?]: Yes.
David Mendenhall: So we'll be returning the money to their heirs.
Kostadis Roussos: If you wish to remain.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, but the guard says, You, sir, are you sure you're not a paladin?
Kostadis Roussos: A paladin.
David Mendenhall: I'm just very confused about why we would be trafficking in stolen goods.
David Mendenhall: Aren't you a guard?
Kostadis Roussos: He pauses.
Kostadis Roussos: You are absolutely correct.
Kostadis Roussos: However, we view it in a different way.
Kostadis Roussos: Outside of the civilized boundaries of Neverwinter's walls, the laws of the laws of Neverwinter do not apply.
Kostadis Roussos: And that is why we need you to go and establish civilization to pacify the areas so that the laws can be done.
David Mendenhall: And once the civilization is established, we should follow those laws.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, but until then, we are in the law of the hinterland.
David Mendenhall: This seems like very grayish to me.
Kostadis Roussos: He points to the city wall.
David Mendenhall[?]: The gray begins at the wall.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: I think we should return the money to the rightful owners.
Kostadis Roussos: The guardsman's eyes sparkle and says, I have an even better idea.
Kostadis Roussos: The city guard has a retirement fund.
David Mendenhall: Well, I know.
David Mendenhall: I mean, if we can't establish who the rightful owners are.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no, no.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm not saying that.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm not saying you should donate it to the city guard retirement fund, where we promise to look aggressively for anyone who might claim this treasure.
Kostadis Roussos: And only if after a suitable amount of time would it fall into the city retirement fund.
Kostadis Roussos: This way, you would know that the money was being guarded and that people would know where to go look for it.
David Mendenhall: Well, I'll think about that.
Kostadis Roussos: I just want you to know that is the if you're concerned.
Kostadis Roussos: I understand your concerns, and that is why I'm very concerned about this.
David Mendenhall: The city guards.
David Mendenhall: You've signed up to be trafficking in stolen goods.
Wade Brown: You haven't signed up for anything yet, have you?
David Mendenhall: Well, I'm desperate.
David Mendenhall: I came to Phandalin for this.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, no, yeah, this is as you haven't left Neverwinter.
Kostadis Roussos: Now, so now you've leave.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I'm just saying.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: So you arrive.
Kostadis Roussos: So along the way, Brewbarry, you know, is really excited about your musical style, has decided to follow you.
Kostadis Roussos: So, you know, you've acquired him as a traveling companion.
Kostadis Roussos: He's very talkative.
Kostadis Roussos: Not.
David Mendenhall: Is he not talkative?
Gary Young [?]: Is he talkative?
UNKNOWN: With notes.
David Mendenhall: What's that?
Gary Young: Love music with notes.
Gary Young [?]: Does Brewbarry periodically try to sing?
Kostadis Roussos [?]: I agree, Brewbarry.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: And less talking, more music.
Kostadis Roussos: And along the way, you guys encounter.
Kostadis Roussos: So how does this drow show up in all of this?
Kostadis Roussos [?]: I'm not quite sure yet.
Gary Young: So, you know, like she grew up in the Drow cities somewhere.
Gary Young: I don't know.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so since you said that, something has happened in the underdark over the last year or so, where the city of the main city of the Drow was completely pulverized by demons that ran wild.
Gary Young: Well, you know, like that tends to happen.
Wade Brown: This wasn't Bob Saget, was it?
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, it was not Bob Saget.
UNKNOWN: I mean, so she could be, you know, that could be what inspired her to become a cleric of the light as she saw the devastation that was brought by worshiping the evil clerics of Lolth and so on and so forth and demonic powers.
UNKNOWN: And, you know, she's had a massive change of heart.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Change of heart.
Gary Young: Yeah, I'm not sure that's entirely the thing.
Gary Young: Like, I'm not going to go through.
Kostadis Roussos: Or maybe she's unimpressed with their power that they let their chosen people die off in that spectacular way and didn't raise a finger.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: It could just be driven out.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, driven out.
Gary Young: Yeah, so like maybe she grew up in the dark and then got an exposure to sunlight, having been forced out of the city, and was like, wow, this is great.
Gary Young: Lathander, though.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, so, you know, if she shows up in Neverwinter, there's likely a temple of Lathander around there.
Gary Young: Yeah, she's like enthralled by the sunlight that's going on and then ends up in Neverwinter, and then there's like a temple of the sun.
UNKNOWN: Oh, my goodness.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: And, you know, the clerics of Lathander are like ecstatic to have this like Drow want to be one of them because it's kind of like proves the righteousness of their god that even the drow would worship.
Gary Young: Sure, yeah.
Gary Young: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: If that worked for them, I'm just telling you why they would be excited by this.
Kostadis Roussos: Like all religious cults, they have their opinions.
UNKNOWN: Okay, so like her first exposure to the sun is a very religious experience.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yes.
Gary Young: She's bored by it and then you know, wanders into town and then keeps going with us.
Gary Young: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: And, you know, since she's interested in paint, but you know, Neverwinter is too civilized.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Too civilized.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, she is a drow.
Kostadis Roussos: There's no assassinations going on.
Kostadis Roussos: There's no torture racks.
Kostadis Roussos: There's, you know, there's no open-air slave markets.
Kostadis Roussos: There's no conspiracies to destroy other noble houses.
Kostadis Roussos: It's all very boring.
Kostadis Roussos: So when she sees the flyer, she decides that this would be more painful.
Gary Young: Yeah, okay.
Gary Young: There we go.
Gary Young: That's a motivation.
Kostadis Roussos: She's like, you know, this is just boring.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, boring.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: And she's learned from hanging out amongst the upper world that people don't take kindly when you rob or kill or torture people at random.
David Mendenhall: I've got to spend money from monsters in this place, though.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, which the drow is totally cool with.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Yeah, yeah, I think we're good with that.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Does the drow know anything about the music player?
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Music?
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, like about like, is Varoujan's music something that the Drow knows about?
Kostadis Roussos: Or is she like, you know, is he so obscure?
David Mendenhall[?]: I don't know why she would care about music.
Kostadis Roussos: Exactly.
David Mendenhall[?]: I'm just saying she would never have heard of his music.
UNKNOWN: That's what I'm asking.
David Mendenhall: That's fine.
Gary Young: I don't think she's necessarily a luck.
Gary Young: So that doesn't work out.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So that's fine.
Kostadis Roussos: She could also have a dim view of music played by Aasimar.
David Mendenhall: Did you know that back at the piano bar, we used to survey the patrons on what they thought of the music?
Gary Young: Aasimar is good.
Gary Young: Yes.
David Mendenhall[?]: That's right.
Gary Young: Or celestial.
Gary Young: Sorry.
Gary Young: That would be something she hasn't seen much of.
Gary Young: And, you know, it's close to a connection to the sun.
Gary Young: Yeah.
Gary Young: Sunlight does he appear.
Gary Young [?]: Okay.
Gary Young [?]: That's good.
Gary Young: All right.
Gary Young: Is she shiny?
David Mendenhall: Anyway, I was going to say Brewbarry is the only patron who ever gave me a 10 out of 10 on the survey.
Gary Young: I think he did.
Gary Young: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So you guys should be seeing the sword coast map.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
UNKNOWN: Yes.
UNKNOWN: I think I have.
UNKNOWN: Okay.
UNKNOWN: Let me just do a few more things.
Kostadis Roussos: There's a couple more locations that I need to make visible.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Wade Brown [?]: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So, and you are arriving in Phandalin.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Gary Young [?]: Where is it?
Gary Young: So this is an uneventful trip along the high road.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: This is, you know, the adventure begins in Phandalin.
Gary Young [?]: All right.
Gary Young: Are we like does like the city guards send out like troops and then maybe we accompany them like part way and then yes or you're a merchant or something like that.
Kostadis Roussos: Merchant caravan after the after the War of the Dragon and the War of the Giants, the the road, the Triboar, the high road has become better patrolled and better guarded.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: So you arrive.
Wade Brown: So we do.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, you do.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me see.
Kostadis Roussos: What am I looking at?
Wade Brown [?]: All right.
Wade Brown: A quaint little town.
Wade Brown [?]: A great little town.
Wade Brown [?]: Little town.
Wade Brown: Doesn't even have a wall, does it?
David Mendenhall[?]: It's a silent village.
Wade Brown: Actually, kind of weird.
Wade Brown: There's like no natural defense.
Wade Brown: There's no water riffer, nothing like that.
David Mendenhall: It's like there was a city wall, but it's been lost to the ages.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So let me just go back to this guy.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
Wade Brown [?]: Hold on.
Wade Brown [?]: Got it.
Wade Brown: Hold on.
Wade Brown: That's just me goofing around.
David Mendenhall: Oh, okay.
Wade Brown: Pink is me, because Kostadis is blue.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: There we go to.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just go back to the right locations.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: So you arrive in Phandalin.
Kostadis Roussos: And right here, you're coming in from Triboar, which I'll make you a little bit bigger so that we can see it.
Kostadis Roussos: And as you pass by, you see a bunch of locations.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just.
Kostadis Roussos: There's actually something I'm supposed to read.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: When nestled in the rocky foothills of the snow-capped mountains, of the snow-capped Sword Mountains, is the mining town of Phandalin, which consists of 40 or 50 simple log buildings.
Kostadis Roussos: Crumbling stone ruins surround the newer houses and shop, showing how this must have been a much larger town in centuries past.
Kostadis Roussos: Phandalin's residents are quiet, hard-working folk who came from distant cities to eke out a life amid the harsh wilderness.
Kostadis Roussos: They are farmers, stonecutters, blacksmiths, traders, prospectors, and children.
Kostadis Roussos: The town has no walls and no garrison.
Kostadis Roussos: Most of the adults keep weapons within easy reach in case the need for arms should arise.
Kostadis Roussos: Visitors are welcome here, especially if they have coin to spend or news to share.
Kostadis Roussos: The Stonehill Inn at the center of the town offers modest meals.
Kostadis Roussos: A couple of doors from the inn posted outside.
Kostadis Roussos: The Townmaster's Hall is a job for adventurers.
Kostadis Roussos: So, I presume you go to the Townmaster's Hall.
Wade Brown: How long have we been walking?
Kostadis Roussos: I'm assuming you've been walking for several days.
Kostadis Roussos: It's kind of like early in the morning.
Kostadis Roussos: Like, it's up to you.
Wade Brown: You know, meals sounds a little better than just running straight to work.
David Mendenhall[?]: All right.
Wade Brown [?]: To the inn.
Wade Brown [?]: Are the meals free?
Wade Brown: Huh?
David Mendenhall: Are the meals free?
Wade Brown: Where have you been living that meals are free?
David Mendenhall: Well, I don't have any money for the meal.
David Mendenhall: I'll just eat my rations outside.
David Mendenhall: You guys go ahead.
Wade Brown: Starving artists.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: So these are, as you're walking by, you see these stores on the left and the right of the road.
Kostadis Roussos: And you, as you, and across the street, you see a Lionshield Coster.
Kostadis Roussos: The famous interdimensional store where one used to be able to buy everything.
Kostadis Roussos: But apparently, rumor has it that their supply chain has been disrupted.
Wade Brown: Damn COVID.
Wade Brown [?]: Terrifying.
Wade Brown [?]: What?
David Mendenhall: Tariffs.
Wade Brown: Oh, tariffs, yeah.
Wade Brown [?]: Sorry, I'm not up to date on my memes.
UNKNOWN: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So you want to go to the Stonehill Inn.
Kostadis Roussos: Is that what I heard?
Wade Brown: I mean, I feel like after traveling for a day, it's just getting off our feet for a while sounds better than getting a negotiation.
Wade Brown: But if the bard has, you know, his drawers, we won't.
David Mendenhall: Maybe I could play for my meal.
Wade Brown: You could sit outside and play and see if you can, you know, upturn your hat or whatever.
David Mendenhall: Maybe people drop some coin performance for money.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, I would do that.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: So the Stonehill Inn was a modest two-story roadhouse.
Kostadis Roussos: It has several rooms for rent on the upper floor.
Kostadis Roussos: And the proprietor is a short, friendly male human named Toblen Stonehill.
Kostadis Roussos: Toblen is very glad to see you.
David Mendenhall[?]: Business is hard for him.
David Mendenhall: Does he know it?
Kostadis Roussos: No, he's very glad to see you.
Kostadis Roussos: Your business.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Right?
Kostadis Roussos: He says hello to you, walks up to a table, starts cleaning it, and says, please sit.
Kostadis Roussos: Rest your weary legs.
Kostadis Roussos: How can I help you?
Wade Brown: Absolutely.
Wade Brown: Tea.
Wade Brown [?]: Tea?
Kostadis Roussos: Tea?
Kostadis Roussos: Just tea?
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Just tea.
Kostadis Roussos: You want me to boil water and give it to you?
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Yes.
Wade Brown: I have the herbs myself if you don't.
Kostadis Roussos: He looks at you, and you're somewhat of a large creature, and he looks at his chair.
Wade Brown: Oh, we're getting to the fat shaving now.
Kostadis Roussos: He says, I think you should sit right here, but if you don't mind, I'd like to get the sturdier chair.
Kostadis Roussos: He comes back.
Kostadis Roussos: He comes back with a sturdier chair.
UNKNOWN: All right.
UNKNOWN: He says, well, that will be 10 copper pieces for the boiled water.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: I assume I have some amount of starting.
David Mendenhall: I want to play for your inn for a while.
David Mendenhall: I have no money.
David Mendenhall: I got a 17 on my performance roll.
UNKNOWN: I'm very good, actually.
Kostadis Roussos: He pauses and says, well, if you have something, one of the more fashionable tunes from Waterdeep or from Neverwinter, I think, or even Triboar.
David Mendenhall: Yes, yes, one of those.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I'd be delighted to hear that.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Of course, that's what those bangers here play Freebird.
David Mendenhall: Yeah, totally.
David Mendenhall: Freebird.
Kostadis Roussos: He seems upset.
David Mendenhall[?]: No, no, no, no, no, no.
UNKNOWN: I'll play whatever you want.
UNKNOWN: Whatever you want.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, Toblen is a little bit upset.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, I didn't realize that.
Kostadis Roussos: My music, if you have some.
David Mendenhall: I'm here to please.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm desperate.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, well, I mean, if you're willing to have one of my creations, I think I could be even entertained by one of yours.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: What are your creations?
Kostadis Roussos: You seem to want to play a music piece of your own.
David Mendenhall: Well, okay.
David Mendenhall: So I can spend the evening playing music.
David Mendenhall: And I don't know if he has a piano, but I have a couple instruments.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Roll your performance to see how well he is.
David Mendenhall: I got a 17.
Kostadis Roussos: He is very impressed with your music.
Kostadis Roussos: He's very delighted.
Kostadis Roussos: As you're playing the music, he goes, Well, that is definitely worth some ale.
Kostadis Roussos: And he pours you a glass of beer and hands it to you.
David Mendenhall: But did you love it?
Kostadis Roussos: He smiles and roll your perception.
Kostadis Roussos: What's your perception?
David Mendenhall: I got a 15 on my perception roll.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, now roll your insight or investigation, whichever one's higher.
David Mendenhall: Four.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, you definitely are not sure whether he's telling the truth.
David Mendenhall: Well, if you didn't love it, I can't take your beer.
Gary Young: With a four, you probably believe him.
Gary Young [?]: Yeah, actually, no, that's true.
UNKNOWN: With a four, you believe him.
David Mendenhall: I believe it.
David Mendenhall: All right.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Well, then I believe it.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, yeah, you did not perceive the lie, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Right, yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: So, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: No, let me try this differently.
Kostadis Roussos: You got the impression that he adored your music.
David Mendenhall: All right.
David Mendenhall: Well, then I will take the beer.
David Mendenhall[?]: Right.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Sometimes it's good to be an idiot.
Kostadis Roussos: Brewbarry.
Kostadis Roussos: Here's his bless.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: All right.
David Mendenhall: So Brewbarry liked it.
David Mendenhall: He's my number one fan.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: So he apparently I'm supposed to reveal a story here.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Excellent.
Gary Young: And I think Valphine was bored with all this display of music.
Gary Young [?]: All right.
Gary Young: We'll say she's not a music lover.
Kostadis Roussos: She goes, once again, the orcs have come down from the mountains to prey on the lowlands.
Kostadis Roussos: If Neverwinter doesn't send help soon, the orcs will overrun Phandalin and destroy everything we work so hard to rebuild.
Kostadis Roussos: Pauses.
Kostadis Roussos: Do you have anything to do with Phandalin?
Kostadis Roussos: Like, are you part of the support Neverwinter is sending to us?
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Yeah, that's right.
David Mendenhall[?]: If there's money in it.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I.
Kostadis Roussos: Ah, money?
Kostadis Roussos: I thought Neverwinter was going to pay you, not us.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, your adventures.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: What gave it away?
David Mendenhall: I don't really understand how we're going to get paid.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, that's very easy, he says.
Kostadis Roussos: Outside the Townmaster's Hall, there is a quest board.
Kostadis Roussos: The Townmaster, the city has some problems, and it's best if you go there and check them out.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Are you dealing with these orcs on that list?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, you'd have to go check what the townmaster has decided is important enough for the city to collect.
Kostadis Roussos: He is, in my mind, I'm not sure how he prioritizes things.
Wade Brown: Do you know why the orcs are causing trouble lately?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, you must have heard of the War of the Dragons and the War of the Giants, followed by the barbarian hordes, followed by the disturbances in the Underdark.
Wade Brown: Oh, the world is always at war.
Wade Brown: What's special about these orcs today?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, usually during these orcs like to expand, and when there isn't a strong army to hold them back, they expand into territories that don't belong to them.
Wade Brown: So, wait, was there a strong army here previously that disbanded?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, the various wars depleted Neverwinter's resources.
Wade Brown [?]: And so.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: This place doesn't look like it ever held a lot of troops in the past, I don't know, 200 years.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, no.
Kostadis Roussos: Phandalin has never been a place with a large army.
Kostadis Roussos: It was overrun by orcs many years ago, but since then it's recovered.
Kostadis Roussos: I, in fact, lived in Triboar and managed to get word about the disaster that came there from the Uthgardt barbarians.
Kostadis Roussos: He looks at you.
Kostadis Roussos: You wouldn't be one of those barbarians, would you?
Kostadis Roussos: I'm so sorry.
Wade Brown: Are you apologizing for your ancestors?
David Mendenhall: I can vouch for him.
David Mendenhall: He really loves music.
Wade Brown [?]: All right.
Wade Brown [?]: He goes.
David Mendenhall: He's not like the other barbarian.
Wade Brown: I've known him a week.
Wade Brown: He seems fine.
Wade Brown [?]: Right.
Wade Brown [?]: He paused.
Kostadis Roussos: What's his name?
Kostadis Roussos: Pauses and goes, look, as far.
Kostadis Roussos: Toblen pauses and goes, look, my friends, I think that whatever plans you might have and whatever adventures you might have and whatever stories you might have, all is forgiven between us.
Kostadis Roussos: The past is the past.
Kostadis Roussos: The future is the future.
David Mendenhall: What are you forgiving me for?
Kostadis Roussos: I'm not forgiving you.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm forgiving all barbarians.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm telling.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm talking about.
David Mendenhall: The barbarian.
Wade Brown [?]: Yes.
David Mendenhall: Oh, yeah.
Wade Brown: He's following a hashtag not all barbarians.
David Mendenhall[?]: Yes, not all barbarians.
David Mendenhall: Well said.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: And so he's like, but I do recommend you go talk to you if you're looking for work.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, if you're looking to spend some money, I don't need a place to stay.
Kostadis Roussos: I do have a room.
Gary Young: Brewbarry.
Gary Young: I can't afford to live here.
Wade Brown: Yeah, I don't think we've got enough money for all of us.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: We'll have to go collect some coin.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, well, in that case, I do recommend you go check the quest board out.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Great.
Wade Brown: All right.
Wade Brown: All roads lead to the quest board.
Wade Brown [?]: We're going to look for the exclamation mark.
Wade Brown [?]: What?
Wade Brown [?]: Look for the exclamation mark.
Wade Brown: The yellow bang.
Gary Young: The quest board with the yellow exclamation mark above it.
David Mendenhall[?]: Yeah, standard MMO.
Gary Young: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
David Mendenhall: The quest marker?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: There.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Do they have us?
Kostadis Roussos: I guess they don't.
Kostadis Roussos: That's really annoying.
Kostadis Roussos: They're not doing that.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So as you're walking across the, as you're about to leave, Toblen says, oh, one minor detail.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Go on.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, when you're outside, just be careful and aware that we do have a small dragon problem.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: The problem with the small or the dragon?
David Mendenhall: Do we get paid if we kill the dragon?
Kostadis Roussos: I'm told the dragons have hordes.
David Mendenhall: People just don't understand.
Wade Brown: Yeah, you guys are all a little too materialistic to robbing from each other.
Wade Brown [?]: All right.
Wade Brown: You know, boiled water is cheap.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, why don't you go?
Kostadis Roussos: So, all right.
Kostadis Roussos: So he says, so do you walk up to the board or do you walk up to the town hall, which is currently boarded up?
David Mendenhall: I feel like a board.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: All right.
David Mendenhall: I'm going to go into a boarded uptown hall.
David Mendenhall[?]: All right.
Gary Young: I think that would be suspicious people.
Gary Young [?]: What?
Gary Young: I don't know that.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: There are three quests on it.
Kostadis Roussos: The first quest is titled Dwarven Excavation Quest.
Wade Brown [?]: Literally named Quest.
UNKNOWN: All right.
Gary Young: Do we need a tab for quests here?
David Mendenhall: We have one under initiative tracking.
David Mendenhall: So what I like party inventory.
David Mendenhall: What was it called?
David Mendenhall: Dwarven What?
Wade Brown [?]: I just put it in the text.
Wade Brown: In the Roll20 chat.
Wade Brown: Yeah.
UNKNOWN: Dwarven Prospectors.
Kostadis Roussos: The second quest is the Gnomengarde quest.
David Mendenhall: Dwarven Prospectors.
David Mendenhall: Rock Gnomes.
David Mendenhall: And Umbrage Hill.
David Mendenhall: Well, now this is real money.
David Mendenhall: You do something, the Townmaster pays you.
David Mendenhall: That's fair.
David Mendenhall: Wow, 50 GP.
David Mendenhall: I haven't had that much money in my whole life.
David Mendenhall: A lot.
Gary Young: Well, I mean, among these options, something that pays more sounds good.
David Mendenhall: Oh, definitely.
David Mendenhall: Why would we do something that pays less?
David Mendenhall: That doesn't make any sense.
Wade Brown [?]: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: So which one do you want to go do?
Wade Brown: I don't know.
Wade Brown: I feel like visiting the midwife.
Wade Brown: That's me.
Wade Brown: That is obviously the cheapest one, too.
Wade Brown: I didn't notice that.
Gary Young: I think I would be leaning towards the gnomes.
Gary Young: That sounds like the most straightforward, doesn't it?
David Mendenhall: Get whatever you can from them.
David Mendenhall: If you bring back something useful and don't want to keep it for yourselves, Townmaster Harbin Wester will pay you 50.
David Mendenhall: Wait, he's going to participate in this thievery scheme?
Wade Brown: This is a sketchy town.
David Mendenhall: No, no.
David Mendenhall: The dwarf prospectors.
Wade Brown [?]: That's honest money.
Wade Brown: I mean, so is the midwife visit.
Wade Brown: It's just a little cheaper.
David Mendenhall: It just doesn't pay as much.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Wade Brown [?]: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So off you go, I presume.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
David Mendenhall: That okay, Drow?
David Mendenhall: Can we do the dwarf prospectors?
Gary Young [?]: It's fine.
Gary Young: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Loki, Dookie.
David Mendenhall: They've been seeking treasure and relics.
David Mendenhall: They're grave robbing?
David Mendenhall: What is wrong with this place?
Wade Brown: This is not a place for us.
Kostadis Roussos: Good God.
Kostadis Roussos: I just want you to know that.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: At what?
Kostadis Roussos: Nothing, nothing.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
David Mendenhall: No, that we're his favorite group of players.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, no, I'm just like, you are by far.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so where are we?
Kostadis Roussos: I just need to go back to the.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so you're on the main map, right?
Wade Brown: Yeah, we're on the Sword Coast or whatever it is.
Wade Brown: Yeah, Sword Coast.
Kostadis Roussos: What is the scale of this map?
Wade Brown: One hex is five miles.
Wade Brown [?]: All right, so that's like 15 miles.
Kostadis Roussos: That's a day's hike.
Kostadis Roussos: So let's go to Icespire Peak.
Wade Brown: Maybe, you know, human speed at my speed, it's like three days.
Kostadis Roussos: What is your speed, by the way?
Wade Brown: No, it's actually 30 feet.
Wade Brown: It's pretty standard.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Oh, you're standard.
Wade Brown [?]: Yeah.
Wade Brown: Yeah.
Wade Brown: It's a little, I mean, it's.
Kostadis Roussos: So, okay, so it's not a, you don't have a, there isn't a pet speed penalty.
Wade Brown: It doesn't appear to be.
Wade Brown: I can't wear armor, which is kind of funny, but you know, also unnecessary for a druid.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep, yep, yep, yep, yep.
Gary Young: Where is it?
Gary Young: Can you crap and scavenge food on our way?
Wade Brown: Oh, I mean, I've got proficiency in survival and nature, right?
Wade Brown: Like, I'm sure I could scavenge food with that stuff.
Wade Brown [?]: Yes.
Wade Brown: There you go.
Wade Brown: Something a little better than some goodberries.
Wade Brown: And it might not kill you.
Wade Brown: I don't know about that role.
Gary Young: It's a little bit.
Wade Brown: But hey, I've got proficiency in nature.
Wade Brown: Oh, no.
Wade Brown: Well, the medicine will also kill you.
Gary Young: Well, at least we have a good look.
Wade Brown: No, I didn't pick any of the conjure food spells.
Gary Young: Goodberry should be on a Druid's spell list, right?
Wade Brown: Maybe not at level one, managed spells.
Wade Brown: Let me check.
Gary Young: Well, it's level one Ranger.
Wade Brown [?]: All right.
Gary Young: So.
UNKNOWN: Oh, good.
UNKNOWN: Okay, I could prepare Goodberries.
UNKNOWN: There you go.
UNKNOWN: I'll take off, I don't know, Longstrider or something.
Wade Brown: Ice knife, I'm never going to use that.
Wade Brown [?]: The journey.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, so I presume you're going normal pace, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Do you want to look for food or do you have rations?
David Mendenhall: I still have two rations that I haven't eaten.
David Mendenhall[?]: All right.
Wade Brown: I'm more of a scavenger, live off the land.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: So you arrive uneventfully at the dwarven excavation location.
Wade Brown: Where is that on this?
Wade Brown: It's southeast, like three hexes, was it?
Gary Young [?]: Yeah, yeah.
Gary Young [?]: So it's right here.
Wade Brown: That's southwest, even though the quest says southeast.
Kostadis Roussos: I get it in the wrong way.
Wade Brown: Oh, sorry, that's Dwarven Prospectors, not the Rock Gnomes.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Yes, you're right.
UNKNOWN: I'm reading the wrong one.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Ignore me.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okie dokie.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Nothing crazy on the way.
David Mendenhall: There's no charge around here.
David Mendenhall[?]: Well done.
UNKNOWN: All right.
Wade Brown: Oh, this is literally just delivering a letter.
Wade Brown: All right.
Wade Brown [?]: It's a fetch quest.
Wade Brown: Well, reverse.
Wade Brown: It's deliver.
David Mendenhall: For the moment.
Wade Brown: Oh, yeah.
Wade Brown: Nothing ever changes on the quest.
Wade Brown: It's set in stone.
David Mendenhall[?]: Exactly.
David Mendenhall: Especially when we change the quest.
Wade Brown: Well, we just do that to troll the GM.
Wade Brown [?]: Totally.
Kostadis Roussos: Are you trying to say something?
Wade Brown [?]: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Wade Brown: Trying.
Wade Brown: Yes.
Wade Brown: C is an Echo 1 for what it's worth.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Do you guys see your characters?
David Mendenhall[?]: No, I just see Echo One.
David Mendenhall: You see black and then E1.
Kostadis Roussos: Ah, why do they not do this?
Wade Brown [?]: Do you see something?
Wade Brown: I still just see Echo 1.
Kostadis Roussos: Can you reload?
Gary Young [?]: Sure.
Wade Brown: Consulting ancient texts.
Wade Brown: Crafting spells.
Wade Brown: Nope.
Wade Brown: Still just Echo 1.
David Mendenhall: No change.
Gary Young: There's pineapple on the pizza then.
Wade Brown: Was that per us?
Kostadis Roussos: You should see something now.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Nope.
David Mendenhall: Nope.
Kostadis Roussos: It's like.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Nope.
Kostadis Roussos: What would you, what are like we see a little circle?
Wade Brown: And we're reloading again.
Wade Brown: Hold on.
David Mendenhall: Nope.
Wade Brown [?]: Nope.
Wade Brown [?]: Ah, that makes part of the problem.
David Mendenhall[?]: Okay, now I see something.
Wade Brown: Excellent.
Wade Brown: I can still see E1, but I can see the camera.
David Mendenhall[?]: We're going into the mine.
David Mendenhall: I see.
Wade Brown [?]: Yeah, hold on.
Wade Brown [?]: I figured out what the problem was.
Wade Brown: Sorry.
Wade Brown: There's another problem.
Wade Brown: I can't grab my token.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, I know.
Kostadis Roussos: That was the problem.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Oh.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Hey, I can grab me now.
Wade Brown [?]: Yes, hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: That was why the character sheets were not, they were not showing.
Kostadis Roussos: Save changes.
Wade Brown [?]: Barbarian's fixed.
Wade Brown [?]: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: I need to just fix the vision on the characters here.
Wade Brown [?]: Yeah, and I can't move the Drow one you're in.
Wade Brown: Yeah, I agree.
Wade Brown: I can only hit the other three.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, the Drow one is the one that you can't see.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: So you should now be able to move it, Gary.
Kostadis Roussos: Can you?
Kostadis Roussos [?]: I can.
UNKNOWN: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm seeing.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep.
UNKNOWN: Everybody can.
UNKNOWN: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: The canyon's rocky walls rise to the height of 80 feet.
Kostadis Roussos: At the end of the canyon, a 20-foot-high wall of black stone has broken the gate carved into it.
Kostadis Roussos: has a broken gate carved into it, with one stone door hanging precariously by a hinge, and the other door missing.
Kostadis Roussos: Beyond this open gate, in the shadow of a great mountain to the east, lies a ruined settlement.
Kostadis Roussos: All is quiet.
Wade Brown [?]: Guys?
Wade Brown: Is there anybody here to deliver the message to?
Kostadis Roussos: I just put the description there.
David Mendenhall: Great.
Kostadis Roussos: So.
David Mendenhall: Why is the gate broken?
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just do something.
Wade Brown: I've heard stories of a white dragon flying around here.
Wade Brown: Perhaps that killed the gate.
David Mendenhall: We are not going to get our 50 GP.
UNKNOWN: Jeez.
Wade Brown: No, no.
Wade Brown: All we have to do is go back and say we delivered the message.
David Mendenhall: But that would be dishonest.
Wade Brown: Fair.
David Mendenhall: Although you do have a point.
Wade Brown: No, no, no.
UNKNOWN: That would be dishonest.
David Mendenhall: Yeah.
Wade Brown: We're here to heal the land, not to, you know, be another blight on it.
Wade Brown [?]: All right.
Wade Brown [?]: So do you want to walk in?
Wade Brown [?]: You walk in?
David Mendenhall: Yes, let's go straight in.
Wade Brown: Send me in first.
David Mendenhall: Yes, no.
David Mendenhall: Who's going in?
David Mendenhall: Oh, you're going. I'll be right behind you.
David Mendenhall: Absolutely.
David Mendenhall[?]: Yes.
Wade Brown: I'm the toughest.
Wade Brown: Also, I got nothing to lose.
Wade Brown: I'm, you know, late in life.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: So a partially collapsed 10-foot high wall separates the courtyard from the settlement west of it.
Kostadis Roussos: Three heaps.
Kostadis Roussos: So are you guys going in?
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: So three heaps of rubble are piled high in this area, hewn from the canyon's back wall.
Kostadis Roussos: A 30-foot-high temple facade features steps rising to the stone platform.
Kostadis Roussos: Facade?
Kostadis Roussos: Did I say facade?
Wade Brown: You did.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Gary Young: So, does it look like it was recently destroyed or a long time ago?
Kostadis Roussos: So this is an excavation.
Gary Young [?]: These are everywhere.
Kostadis Roussos: These are archaeologists.
Wade Brown: Grave robbers.
Kostadis Roussos: Everybody's a critic.
Wade Brown: What do you like?
Wade Brown: Lawful, super lawful?
Kostadis Roussos: No, very confused.
Kostadis Roussos: Three feet heaps of rubble are piled high in this area, hewn from the canyon's back wall.
Kostadis Roussos: A 30-foot-high temple facade features steps rising to a stone platform.
Kostadis Roussos: Cut into this facade is a 10-foot-high open doorway flanked by crumbling, life-sized granite statues of cloaked dwarves.
Kostadis Roussos: Evil grins can be seen on their weather-worn faces.
David Mendenhall: Is there statues?
David Mendenhall: It's dwarves that are excavating a dwarven ruin.
David Mendenhall: Is that correct?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, as you, do you guys, are you stealthily walking here or are you kind of like having a message?
Wade Brown: I had no intention of being stealthy.
David Mendenhall: No, no.
UNKNOWN: All right.
David Mendenhall[?]: So, loud.
David Mendenhall[?]: It's an excavation.
UNKNOWN: There's bombs and stuff going off, right?
Wade Brown [?]: Very naive.
David Mendenhall: We're level one.
David Mendenhall[?]: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: The two dwarves are very excited.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Oh, sorry.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: You said they were statues.
UNKNOWN: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: No, no, the statues are like.
Wade Brown: Are they these little star things?
Wade Brown [?]: Yeah, those are the star things.
Wade Brown [?]: Okay.
Wade Brown [?]: All right.
David Mendenhall: They're very excited.
David Mendenhall: Okay, I'll rush up to talk to them.
David Mendenhall: I have a high charisma.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, he's like chewing.
Kostadis Roussos: He's like, Dazlyn goes, I'll just have you note that this is a private excavation, and everything that we're doing, we're not sharing.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Yeah.
David Mendenhall: So we're here from Townmaster Harbin.
David Mendenhall: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
David Mendenhall: And he wanted us to give you a message.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, how kind of him?
Kostadis Roussos: What was the message?
David Mendenhall: There's a white dragon coming here to kill you.
Wade Brown: Here there be dragons.
Wade Brown [?]: Well, okay, guys.
Wade Brown [?]: We did it.
David Mendenhall: Let's go.
Wade Brown: Let's go get our money.
Wade Brown [?]: Yep.
Wade Brown [?]: Right.
Wade Brown [?]: I mean, that's all the quest said.
David Mendenhall: I'm walking.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, oh, hold on, hold on, hold on.
UNKNOWN: Before you.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes?
David Mendenhall: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes.
David Mendenhall: Did you need something?
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, well, you know, do you see the back?
Kostadis Roussos: Norbus goes, well, my name is Norbus in Ironrune, and I'm a Shield Dwarf Prospector.
Kostadis Roussos: And Dazlyn Grayshard over here is my partner.
Kostadis Roussos: And yeah, we've been looking for mountains in the southwest of Phandalin.
Kostadis Roussos: And we decided to explore this cabin and we found startling evidence of an ancient dwarven settlement buried by an avalanche.
David Mendenhall: Are these your ancestors?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, not my ancestors per se, but they are somebody's ancestors.
David Mendenhall: Are you working on behalf of their ancestors?
Kostadis Roussos: Could Guy just continue?
Kostadis Roussos: This is considered.
Kostadis Roussos: He pauses and goes, no, no, but it's important to hear the rest of the story.
Kostadis Roussos: Now, normally I would be very objected.
Kostadis Roussos: I would object terribly to anyone excavating and digging into Dwarven, the Dwarven Dead, but this happens to be an old temple of Abbathor, the evil god of greed.
Gary Young: Do I know anything about Abbathor?
UNKNOWN: Religion checks here.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Anybody do better than that?
David Mendenhall: Four.
Gary Young [?]: I'm not very religious.
David Mendenhall: Any more roles, guys.
David Mendenhall: Two more.
David Mendenhall: Go for it, Gary.
Gary Young: I said 14.
David Mendenhall: Oh, 14.
David Mendenhall: Nice.
Gary Young: Yeah.
Gary Young: Am I not displaying this properly?
David Mendenhall: Nice.
Wade Brown [?]: It's just a story.
Wade Brown [?]: Excuse me.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, well, so you pause, look around, and say, let me see if I can get this straight.
Kostadis Roussos: Abbathor, during a solar eclipses, Abbathor is appeased with sacrifices of blood and gemstone.
Kostadis Roussos: Dazlyn goes, Yes, yes, yes, that's exactly right.
Kostadis Roussos: And then you add, and on one occasion, the god found the sacrifices of this temple's priests lacking, so he caused an earthquake, and that avalanche collapsed the parts of the temple and buried the settlement.
Gary Young: So is Abbathor a god I know from the drow cities?
Kostadis Roussos: No, but it's like one of the evil dwarven god of greed.
Kostadis Roussos: You know, it's one of those things that I see.
Gary Young [?]: Okay.
Gary Young [?]: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: You're kind of projecting what an evil drow god would do.
Kostadis Roussos: So they're not saying.
Gary Young: Yeah.
Gary Young: I mean, like, there's no news here.
Kostadis Roussos: It's like, right.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, Dazlyn looks at you and goes, yes, but I'll have you note that Dwarven gods are not like your drow gods.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: It's fine.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Although Norbus go punches in, she's a cleric of Lathander.
Kostadis Roussos: A dwarven cleric of Lathander.
Kostadis Roussos: A drow cleric of Lathander.
David Mendenhall: It's got unheard of.
Kostadis Roussos: There's like, I'm telling you, she's lying.
Kostadis Roussos: No, she's that's that.
Kostadis Roussos: That's definitely the symbol.
Kostadis Roussos: Are you really a cleric of Lathander?
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Well, yes.
Wade Brown [?]: Why, indeed.
Wade Brown [?]: He's so gloriously bright.
David Mendenhall[?]: Yes.
David Mendenhall: Can I cast a light spell on you?
Gary Young: Yeah.
Room (not at table): Are you going to make coffee?
Kostadis Roussos: No, there's a whole other bag of coffee.
Room (not at table): No, but you're going to make it, right?
Room (not at table): Yes, yes.
Room (not at table): Okay.
Room (not at table): Was the child coding?
Room (not at table): Yes.
Room (not at table): Did you tell people the story?
Kostadis Roussos: All right, we'll tell it to them in a little bit.
Room (not at table): But I want to hear the story.
Room (not at table): The child was coding.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: So I come home, and Nick suddenly disappears into his bedroom.
Room (not at table): How did you hear the story?
Kostadis Roussos: So Nick disappears into his bedroom.
Wade Brown: For context, I would like to know how old Nick is.
Wade Brown [?]: 14.
Room (not at table): Thank you.
Room (not at table): 15 almost.
Kostadis Roussos: Almost 15.
Kostadis Roussos: So he walks into his bedroom and he doesn't say anything.
Kostadis Roussos: And it's the end of the school day, and I figured that he went and go and play with his computer games or whatever.
Kostadis Roussos: He's been quiet for about an hour and a half.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm like, okay, I probably should go and tell him that, you know, enough playing with computers.
Kostadis Roussos: Does something useful with your life?
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, whatever.
Kostadis Roussos: I was like, more to the point where if you're going to spend all that, let's go do something together, right?
Kostadis Roussos: Let's go get dinner.
Kostadis Roussos: Let's let's whatever.
Kostadis Roussos: Mom was out.
Kostadis Roussos: So he then texts me.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me see if I have any text.
Wade Brown [?]: This is going to look great in the AI summary.
Kostadis Roussos: It goes, it goes.
David Mendenhall: The AI will be very confused by this section.
Kostadis Roussos: I did it in all caps.
Kostadis Roussos: And I'm like, okay, I guess you defeated some big bat and some monster, right?
Kostadis Roussos: That's what my brain's going.
Kostadis Roussos: I fixed the bug that I've been trying to fix for the past two hours.
Kostadis Roussos: Holy, let's go.
Kostadis Roussos: Finally.
David Mendenhall: What's he working on?
UNKNOWN: That's funny.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, he was working on a game and he missed an assignment.
Kostadis Roussos: He didn't have an assignment.
Kostadis Roussos: And he was very excited because he was finally able to debug the code because it's in Python.
Kostadis Roussos: And he printed out.
Kostadis Roussos: He was putting printfs everywhere.
Kostadis Roussos: And then he said, what if I printf the object?
Kostadis Roussos: And the object printed out the values in the object.
Kostadis Roussos: He was able to debug it.
Kostadis Roussos: So he was very proud of himself.
Wade Brown [?]: Awesome.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: But it was very funny, me like going, I finally did it.
Kostadis Roussos: I'm like, okay, I'm going to have to show enthusiasm about you defeating some monster in some game.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, I can do this.
Kostadis Roussos: I can do it.
Wade Brown: Psyching yourself up.
Kostadis Roussos: I can do this.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Room (not at table): I just promised tell David Mendenhallthat when he says polymorphism, it's beautiful.
Room (not at table): I'm going to tape it for him.
Gary Young [?]: Oh, my God.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Oh, Jesus.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, Nick did say, I now understand the value of polymorphism.
Kostadis Roussos: Did he really?
Room (not at table): He understood the value of classes.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Today he understood the value of classes.
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, because you could put all the code that's related to each other in the same place.
David Mendenhall: Times of programming.
David Mendenhall: What a concept.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Oh, to be 14 again.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: You know, there's these moments as a parent where you want to burst their bubble and then you're like, no, no, some things need to be burst in their own time.
Wade Brown: Like Santa.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Leave that for the world to do.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Santa.
Room (not at table): Santa.
Room (not at table): My dog.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Let's get back.
Kostadis Roussos: That's Wade's dog.
Gary Young [?]: Dog?
Kostadis Roussos: That's a dog.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Room (not at table): But there's a dog.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, I know.
Kostadis Roussos: I know.
Room (not at table): Okay, bye.
Room (not at table): Bye, thank you.
David Mendenhall: Bye, Sasha.
David Mendenhall: Happy birthday.
Kostadis Roussos: Happy birthday.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Room (not at table): Yes.
Room (not at table): Not yet, but soon.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Soon.
Kostadis Roussos: So Dazlyn and Norbus, after they have their like five minutes worth of talking, goes, let me say something.
Kostadis Roussos: You know, we're just prospectors.
David Mendenhall: We're just messengers.
Kostadis Roussos: But I agree.
Kostadis Roussos: We have a business proposition for you.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
Wade Brown: We should at least hear them out.
Wade Brown: Talking is a free action, right?
Kostadis Roussos: What about listening?
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, I, well, if you were willing to go in there and deal with any nasties and beasties, we would be willing to give you two sending stones.
Wade Brown: Oh, those weren't?
UNKNOWN: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Yeah.
UNKNOWN: They're basically like walkie-talkies.
UNKNOWN: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Wade Brown [?]: I mean.
UNKNOWN: Are those valuable?
Kostadis Roussos: Well, we also even you would know that magical items are valuable.
David Mendenhall: I'm not sure about that.
Gary Young: We also get the 50 gold pieces.
Gary Young [?]: What?
David Mendenhall: Well, we're already going to get the 50 gold pieces.
David Mendenhall: All we have to do is go back to the town and we can get the 50 gold pieces.
Wade Brown: Yeah.
Wade Brown: We just, our job here was to deliver the message.
Wade Brown: The sending stones would allow you to project your music to two ends at one time.
Wade Brown: Just saying.
Gary Young: So it's Brewbarry is like, does that mean I can listen to music all the time?
Wade Brown: Well, at the other end of the, you know, the matching stone or whatever has a musician on the other end.
Wade Brown: Yes.
Wade Brown [?]: So.
David Mendenhall: Well, maybe we can sell them.
David Mendenhall: They're probably worth something.
Wade Brown: Do you have any idea what's in there?
Wade Brown: Asking the dwarves what lies beyond.
Wade Brown: You just said, you know, take care of some nasties and beasties.
Wade Brown: What have you seen?
David Mendenhall: So what do you, what do you say more about what you're expecting us to do?
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I mean, just go inside and if you see anything that is dangerous, kill it.
Wade Brown: Do we look dangerous?
Kostadis Roussos: If you were bad people, yes.
David Mendenhall: I just want to be clear.
David Mendenhall: All of the treasure, you call it, relics, all of that stuff, you're going to be returning that to the rightful owners, correct?
David Mendenhall[?]: Yes, of course.
David Mendenhall: Okay, so we'll consider for you.
Wade Brown: Make sure they don't consider themselves the rightful owners.
David Mendenhall: Oh.
David Mendenhall: That's good, mate.
Wade Brown: How green are you?
Gary Young: We're level one.
Wade Brown [?]: I mean, come on.
David Mendenhall: My whole life studying music and nothing else.
David Mendenhall: What do you think?
Wade Brown: You kids, you whipper snappers.
Wade Brown [?]: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: So, you don't have to come.
Kostadis Roussos: You don't have to do this.
Kostadis Roussos: You can come back later to go help them.
Kostadis Roussos: There's no requirement to do things in any particular order.
David Mendenhall: Right, sure.
Kostadis Roussos: Just want to make sure.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: I've already made the day's journey.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: So you will go in?
Wade Brown: We may as well have a look around and decide, you know, if it's worth our effort.
Wade Brown [?]: All right.
David Mendenhall[?]: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Can someone put you guys in the right marching order?
Wade Brown: It'll be me up front. Does anybody have a passive perception of 15? No. Not me. Oh, all right. Oh, man. We need a ranger. Let's go with this as the. Wait, passive perception.
Wade Brown: Valphine has 15.
Wade Brown [?]: Oh, she does?
Gary Young [?]: Wait, are you kidding me?
Gary Young: Passive perception 15?
Gary Young: Yeah.
Gary Young [?]: Oh, look at it.
Kostadis Roussos: It's on the internet.
Gary Young [?]: I was going to say, wait, how could a character of Gary's not have high perception?
Gary Young: Well, you know, she's just got high wisdom.
David Mendenhall[?]: That helps.
Gary Young [?]: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Gary, you're a trope.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Aren't we all?
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Like, everybody's a trope of some kind.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I know, but Gary's characters always have high perception.
David Mendenhall[?]: It's also happening.
Gary Young [?]: Yeah, because they've been rogues and clerics.
Gary Young: And rangers, I guess.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, yeah, rogues with clerics and rangers.
Kostadis Roussos: You can't have low perception.
Kostadis Roussos: It's just an it's a flute.
Kostadis Roussos: That's right.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: It's anathema.
Kostadis Roussos: So your characters always have high perception.
Room (not at table): They fed the dogs, right?
Kostadis Roussos: I believe so, yes.
Room (not at table): They're not.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, he did feed them.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: You notice a secret door.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Oh, is that the S?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, that is the S.
Wade Brown: Can you tell us about it?
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: Norbus, however, says, well, before you go any deeper, I think it's only fair that we tell you what we did discover.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: We did ask.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: We did see an ochre jelly. Oh, dear. Bad. What? That's not so bad. Yes, it was bad.
Kostadis Roussos: I mean, just very dangerous creatures.
Kostadis Roussos: We ran out before we could face them.
Gary Young: Aren't those really bad?
Kostadis Roussos: He goes, Norbus goes, look, we are dwarven prospectors and explorers.
Kostadis Roussos: I don't know whether what makes a dangerous monster or an easy monster.
Kostadis Roussos: You've got swords and you know how to cast spells and you have a buff shell.
Wade Brown: The shell doesn't help me, you know, eliminate the jelly.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, I mean, what I'm trying to say is that you seem to me as powerful, worthy adventurers.
David Mendenhall: We're all levels.
Wade Brown [?]: Stones are worth a lot of money, guys.
UNKNOWN: Come on.
Wade Brown: Wait, how much?
David Mendenhall: I don't know.
David Mendenhall: I think we might be able to get like a couple hundred gold pieces for them.
Wade Brown: Well, that would be a big, big update.
Wade Brown: But we need to keep ourselves alive.
Wade Brown: Oh, sure.
David Mendenhall: Jelly.
David Mendenhall: When your alternative is starving, you're willing to take some risks.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So, would you want to go down the secret door or definitely the secret door?
David Mendenhall: I've never been through a secret door.
David Mendenhall: That sounds cool.
Wade Brown [?]: All right.
David Mendenhall: I'll go first.
Wade Brown: Oh, really?
Wade Brown: You'll delete the chart.
Wade Brown: All right.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
David Mendenhall: C of 13, I'll be fine.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: You know.
Kostadis Roussos: You arrive at a door.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: A door.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Is it a secret door?
Kostadis Roussos: No, no.
Kostadis Roussos: There's a door.
Kostadis Roussos: You can see what you should be able to see what you're seeing.
Wade Brown: Regular.
Wade Brown: Yeah, we see a little hallway with like a door here at the end of it, I think.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, so what do you do?
Kostadis Roussos: Go through the door to the north or the door to the west?
Wade Brown [?]: East.
Kostadis Roussos: Ah, east, actually.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, to through the door to the east.
Wade Brown: We are blacked off.
Kostadis Roussos: You are?
Kostadis Roussos: I don't see anything past the east door.
UNKNOWN: It's there.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: Let me just.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: There we go.
Kostadis Roussos: This is like, this is old school.
Wade Brown: There we go.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: There you go.
Kostadis Roussos: Here you go.
Kostadis Roussos: Let's see.
Kostadis Roussos: And then we'll stop here.
Kostadis Roussos: An earthquake collapsed part of this room, which holds nothing of value.
Kostadis Roussos: Wow.
David Mendenhall: That's where we're stopping.
David Mendenhall: Come on.
David Mendenhall: I mean, if that's it, then let's go through the other door.
Wade Brown [?]: Yeah.
Wade Brown [?]: Hit the door.
Wade Brown [?]: All right.
David Mendenhall[?]: Okay.
UNKNOWN: Nothing at value.
UNKNOWN: All right.
UNKNOWN: I'll go through.
Kostadis Roussos: Are you going to go through?
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on.
Kostadis Roussos: I have to fix the lighting mic.
Kostadis Roussos: Yep.
Kostadis Roussos: And roll a perception.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: I'm assuming anything.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Does anybody.
Kostadis Roussos: So you reach the end of a hallway and there's a door.
David Mendenhall: Valphine, do you see anything?
Kostadis Roussos: Valphine?
Gary Young: No, I don't.
Gary Young [?]: No, no.
David Mendenhall: Well, I mean, if you really want me to look, I guess I can look.
UNKNOWN: I'm just not very good at looking for things like that.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
David Mendenhall: Like I said, I didn't see anything.
Kostadis Roussos: Roll an investigation, rather.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Nope.
Kostadis Roussos: Nope.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Kostadis Roussos: You find there's curiously door, but as you're looking for it,
Wade Brown: ochre jellies falls on your heads.
Wade Brown [?]: No.
David Mendenhall: Oh, there's a secret door.
Wade Brown: This doesn't seem like a very useful passage.
Wade Brown: It looks like it takes us right back to where we had been.
Kostadis Roussos: All right.
Wade Brown [?]: So there's, yes, the passageway leads north that way.
Wade Brown [?]: Okay.
David Mendenhall: Odd.
Wade Brown: Yeah, that is a weird, weird layout.
Wade Brown: I wonder what this.
Wade Brown: There must have been something in that earthquake room at some point.
David Mendenhall[?]: Yeah.
UNKNOWN: Did we search in there?
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, you did.
Kostadis Roussos: There was nothing of any value.
David Mendenhall: Nothing of value.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: No signs of other exits or anything.
David Mendenhall[?]: No, no.
Gary Young [?]: Weird.
David Mendenhall: Did we clear the rubble?
Gary Young: In the big room, did we?
Gary Young [?]: No, you have not gone into the big room.
David Mendenhall: I've never gone into the big room.
Kostadis Roussos: This is the partially collapsed room.
Kostadis Roussos: Hold on, let me write it down.
David Mendenhall: So if I go back in here, is there can I clear the rubble?
Kostadis Roussos: Can you clear the rubble?
David Mendenhall: But it's only partially collapsed.
David Mendenhall: It's not fully collapsed.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay, so you're still dead.
UNKNOWN: It's still alive.
David Mendenhall: That's right.
David Mendenhall: Slightly alive.
Wade Brown [?]: So let's see.
Wade Brown: You just move the text where we can't read it.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah, I know.
Kostadis Roussos: It's like, hold on.
Wade Brown [?]: It's good there.
Wade Brown [?]: It's not in there anyway.
Kostadis Roussos: There it is.
Kostadis Roussos: No, it was just an it was just annoying me.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, okay.
Kostadis Roussos: So you're digging in the partially collapsed room.
Kostadis Roussos: And so you continue to dig.
Kostadis Roussos: But after a certain amount of digging, well, it's possible that things could get disrupted and rolled around.
Kostadis Roussos: Do you want to just keep digging, take your chances, or like think about it a little bit more?
Gary Young: I think we should look around more.
Gary Young: This seems unproductive.
Wade Brown: I still have architectural questions about this place that make this room very interesting.
David Mendenhall: Well, they were mining it and it kind of collapsed while they were mining it.
Wade Brown: Was it a room or a mine shaft?
UNKNOWN: Like, what is it?
UNKNOWN: Like, how furnished is this room or finished, I should say?
David Mendenhall: It's just a cave.
Kostadis Roussos: No, so remember, this is part of a temple complex.
Kostadis Roussos: So who knows what?
Kostadis Roussos: So since you asked, and since I can provide, oh, dear.
Kostadis Roussos: I reach for the books.
Kostadis Roussos: Let's see.
Kostadis Roussos: There's usually something I can get here.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: So the wall has several protruding blocks.
Kostadis Roussos: As you look at them, they're designed to allow defenders within the chamber to gain cover from one of the chamber's entrances.
Wade Brown: There's only one entrance in the chamber.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, yes.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Well, currently.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes, currently.
Kostadis Roussos: And so, what you gather from the position of these things is that there was an entrance on the other side that this room connects to another part to the northeast, west, east, yes, northeast.
David Mendenhall: But it's no longer accessible.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
David Mendenhall: All right.
UNKNOWN: Well, thanks, guys.
David Mendenhall[?]: All right.
Gary Young [?]: Are you going to try to play next week?
Kostadis Roussos [?]: We'll try.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
UNKNOWN: Excellent.
Kostadis Roussos: Well, that's all we can ask for is to try.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: There is no try.
Kostadis Roussos: Oh, by the way, Gary, I'm going to tell you something.
Kostadis Roussos: Time shifter.
Kostadis Roussos: Get the app time shifter.
Gary Young: Oh, this is for changing time zones.
Kostadis Roussos: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos: I swear it has been life-changing in my experience over the last two, three years.
Kostadis Roussos: It is not, it's not really hokey.
Kostadis Roussos: It just tells you when to go to sleep.
Kostadis Roussos: And if you want to spend like five days adjusting your time schedule, it works.
UNKNOWN: And if you just want to adjust it the day before, it also does a lot of value.
Kostadis Roussos: So I travel a lot to Greece and it has definitely made the travel to Greece and the travel back a lot easier from a time zone perspective.
David Mendenhall[?]: Yes.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Okay, great.
Kostadis Roussos: So like, and five times I've done it.
Kostadis Roussos: So at this point in time, I'm pretty, I'm a pretty satisfied customer.
Gary Young: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos [?]: Thank you.
Kostadis Roussos: Okay.
David Mendenhall[?]: I strongly recommend.
David Mendenhall[?]: Anybody else?
UNKNOWN: All right.
UNKNOWN: To anybody else as well.
UNKNOWN: All right, guys.
Kostadis Roussos: But I know David Mendenhallcan handle time zone shifts because he is.
David Mendenhall: I've never done India, though.
David Mendenhall: I'm a little bit worried about that one.
Kostadis Roussos: It's not, well, if you've done Bulgaria, it's only like three more hours, four more hours.
David Mendenhall: Okay.
Kostadis Roussos: Right.
Kostadis Roussos: So, I mean, you go to Romania, you've been to Romania, right?
David Mendenhall: Yes, yes.
Kostadis Roussos: Yeah.
Kostadis Roussos: So it's not that much worse.
Kostadis Roussos: All right, man.
Kostadis Roussos: Good night, guys.
Kostadis Roussos: Bye.